Guide to the Andrew F. Smith Collection of Cookery Ephemera MSS.295
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Cookery Ephemera, 1798-2009
  - Church & Dwight Company, Inc., 1913-1959 (Box 8, Folder 1, Box 7, Folder 13-15)
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee. Successful Baking for Flavor and Texture. 3rd edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Company, Inc., 1935.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee. Successful Baking for Flavor and Texture. 5th edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Company, Inc., 1936.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee. Successful Baking for Flavor and Texture. 7th edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Company, Inc., 1937.
  - C.I. Hood & Company Apothecaries, 1890-1905 (Box 8, Folder 2-4)
    Hood & Co. Hood's Combined Cook Books. Number One; Number Two; Number Three. High-Street Cook Book. By the Ladies of High-Street Church. Lowell, MA: C. I. Hood & Co., circa 1890.
    Hood & Co. Hood's Cook Book. Number one. Reprint. Lowell, MA: C. I. Hood & Co., undated.
    Hood & Co. Hood's Cook Book Number Two. Lowell, MA: C. I. Hood & Co., undated.
    Hood & Co. Left Overs or Economy in the Kitchen. Lowell, MA: C. I. Hood & Co., 1891.
    Hood & Co. Hood's Pickles and Preserves Etcetera. Lowell, MA: C. I. Hood, 1898.
    C. I. Hood Co. Hood's Book of Home-Made Candies No. 2. Lowell, MA: C. I. Hood Co., 1905.
  - C.J. Van Houton & Zoon Cocoa; Cleveland Brothers, Cleveland Baking Powder Company, circa 1896 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Cleveland Baking Powder Co. Cleveland's Superior Receipts. New York, NY: Cleveland Baking Powder Co., undated.
    Cleveland Baking Powder Co. Cleveland's Superior Receipts. 10th million with supplement. New York, NY: Cleveland Baking Powder Co., undated.
    C. J. Van Houton. Van Houton's Pure Soluble Cocoa. Place of publication unknown: C. J. Van Houton, undated.
  - Clearfield Cheese Company, Inc.; The Cleveland Foundry Company, 1912-circa 1940s (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Clearfield Cheese Co. Delicious Recipes Suggested by Clearfield; Valuable Coupon on the Inside. Curwensville, PA: Clearfield Cheese Co., undated.
    Cleveland Foundry Co. New Perfection Cook-Book. Cleveland, OH: Cleveland Fouundatedry Co., 1912.
  - C.L. Jones & Company; Clover Brand Egg Company, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    C. L. Jones & Co. Parloa, Maria. About Bread. Boston, MA: C. L. Jones & Co., undated.
  - Club Aluminum Company, circa 1925 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Club Aluminum Company. The Recipe Book for Club Aluminum Ware with Personal Service. Chicago, IL: Club Aluminum Company, circa 1925.
  - The Cocoanut Manufacturing Company, Ltd.; Code, Elfelt & Company, 1880, 1885 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    The Cocoanut Manufacturing Company. Cocoanut and Its Preparation. New York, NY: The Cocoanut Manufacturing Company, 1885.
    Code, Elfelt & Co. Order form, Manufacturers of Pickles and Hermetically Sealed Goods. San Francisco, CA: Code, Elfelt & Co., 1880.
  - Coffee Research; Tea Research, circa 1900-1925, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Cheek-Neal Coffee Co. The Story of Coffee and How to Make It. Nashville, Houston, Jacksonville, Richmond, NY, Los Angeles: Cheek-Neal Coffee, Co., 1925.
    Gillies Coffee Co. The Story of Coffee. New York, NY: Gillies Coffee Co., undated.
    Lipton. 7 Delicious Recipes from Lipton Flavored Tea. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
    Stephen Leeman Products. Ming Tea Dictionary. West Nyack, NY: Stephen Leeman Products, undated.
  - Colgate & Company, 1885 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Colgate & Co. The Ideal Receipt Book. New York, NY: Colgate & Co., 1885.
  - Colonial Baking Company; Colonial Molasses Company, Inc., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Colonial Baking Co. Colonial Weekly Bulletin, Fruit-Nut Cake. Place of publication unknown: Colonial Baking Company, March 17-23, 1944.
    Colonial Molasses Co. Inc. Colonial Molasses Home Recipes; A Collection of Favorite Recipes. New Orleans, LA; Jersey City, NJ: Colonial Molasses Co., Inc., undated.
  - Connecticut Dairy and Food Council; Continental Baking Company, Inc., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Connecticut Dairy and Food Council. Lunches for School Children. Hartford, CT: Connecticut Dairy and Food Council, undated.
    Continental Baking Company. The Wonder Book of Good Meals; World's Fair Edition. New York, NY: Continental Baking Company, Inc., 1934.
  - Connecticut Pop Corn Co., undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Cook & Phillips Grocers; Copeland Sales Company with Elizabeth Mann Clark, circa 1900, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Cook & Phillips. Catalogue Issued by Cook & Phillips. Ballston Spa, NY: Journal Print., circa 1900.
    Copeland Sales Company. Clark, Elizabeth Mann. 21 New Recipes for Frozen Desserts. Detroit, MI: Evans-Winter-Webb, 1926.
  - Cornell University; G. L. F. Exchange; New York State Food Commission, 1914-2006 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Corn Products Refining Company, circa 1900-1920s, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    Corn Products Refining Company. Proven Recipes Showing the Uses of the Three Great Products from Corn. New York, NY: Corn Products Refining Co., undated.
    Corn Products Refining Company. Hewitt, Emma Churchman. Corn Products Cook Book. New York, NY: Corn Products Refining Co., undated.
    Corn Products Refining Company. Armstrong, Helen. Karo in the Kitchen. New York, NY: Corn Products Refining Co., 1903.
    Corn Products Refining Company. Hewitt, Emma Churchman. Karo Cook Book. New York, NY: Corn Products Refining Company, 1910.
    Corn Products Refining Company. Mazola Recipes for Salads, Cakes and Fried Foods. New York, NY: Best Foods Division of Con Products Company, undated.
    Corn Products Refining Company. Hewitt, Emma Churchman. Corn Products Cook Book. New York, NY: Corn Products Refining Company, undated.
  - Corning Glass Works, 1924, circa 1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Corning Glass Works. Pyrex. Corning, NY: Corning Glass Works, 1924.
    Corning. Microwave Cooking: Corning Helps You Make the Most of It. Corning, NY: Corning Glass Works, circa 1981.
  - Coral Reed Nurseries Company; The Cotton Oil Product Company, circa 1888, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Coral Reef Nurseries Company. Avocados with Ancestors. Bulletin No. 3. Homestead, FL: Coral Reef Nurseries Company, July 1, 1921.
    Cotton Oil Product Co. Some Things about Lard. New York, NY: Cotton Oil Product Co., circa 1888.
  - Country Herbs, Stockbridge, MA; Coyle, McCandlish & Company, 1885, circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Coyle, McCandish & Co. Monthly Price List. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, August 1885.
  - The Cracker Jack Company, circa 1910-1920s (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Cracker Jack Co. Angelus Recipes, One Taste Invites Another. New York, NY and Chicago, IL: The Cracker Jack Co., circa 1910.
    Cracker Jack Co. Angelus Recipes, One Taste Invites Another. Place of publication unknown: The Cracker Jack Co., circa 1920.
  - Cranberry Research, circa 1910-1960s (Box 9, Folder 7)
    American Cranberry Exchange. Eatmor [sic] Cranberries; Tasty Ways to Serve the Tonic Fruit. New York, NY: American Cranberry Exchange, undated.
    American Cranberry Exchange. Eatmor Cranberries Tasty Ways to Serve the Tonic Fruit. New York, NY: American Cranberry Exchange, undated.
    American Cranberry Exchange. Eatmor [sic] Cranberries; 44 Ways to Serve the Tasty Fruit. New York, NY: American Cranberry Exchange, undated.
    Cranberry Canners, Inc. "6 Ways to Serve Ocean Spray Cranberry Sauce." South Hanson, MA: Cranberry Canners, Inc., undated.
    Indian Trail Foods, Inc. Quick Frozen Cranberry with Orange. Wisconsin Rapids, WI: Indian Trail Foods, Inc., undated.
    National Cranberry Association (Ocean Spray). 20 Famous Cranberry Dishes. from Famous American Eating Places. Place of publication unknown: National Cranberry Association, undated.
    New England Cranberry Sales Company. Cranberry Receipt Book. Place of publication unknown: New England Cranberry Sales Company, circa 1910.
  - Cream of Wheat Company; Crescent Manufacturing Company, circa 1900 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Cream of Wheat Co. Cream of Wheat A Dainty Breakfast. Place of publication unknown: Cream of Wheat Co., undated.
  - Crown Mills with Mrs. L. A. Humphreys, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Crown Mills. Humphreys, Mrs. L. A. Choice Recipes. Portland, OR: Crown Mills, undated.
    Crown Mills. Sandwich Book of All Nations; 400 New Ways of Making Delicious Sandwiches. Portland, OR: Crown Mills, 1942.
  - Cudahy Packing Company, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Cudahy Packing Co. A Story of Puritan "First in the Land. Place of publication unknown: Cudahy Packing Co., circa 1928.
  - Culinary Archives & Museum, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Culinary Arts Institute, 1940-1975 (Box 9, Folder 12-14, Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Culinary Arts Press, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Culinary Historians of New York, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - The Cultivator, Vol. IX, No. 6, 1852 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cummins, Mrs. H. Y., 1886 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Curtice Brothers Company, 1890-1908 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Curtice Brothers Co. Rochester Preserving House. Price List of Extra Quality New York State Canned Fruits, Vegetables, Meats and other Table Delicacies. Rochester, NY: Curtice Brothers Co., 1890.
    Curtice Brothers Co. Original Menus. Rochester, NY: Curtice Brothers Company, 1908.
  - Curtice-Burns, Inc., circa 1970-1980s (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Silver Floss Foods. The Sauerkraut Book. Phelps, NY: Silver Floss Foods, undated.
  - Curtis Davis & Company, 1872 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    A. Stowell & Co. The Cuisine. Second Edition. Boston, MA: Fox and Company, publishers, Alfred Mudge and Son, printers, 1872.
  - Curtiss Candy Company--Baby Ruth Gum, 1929 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 7)
  - Cushman's Bakery; C. Y. Schelly & Brother, circa 1920-1940s (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Cushman. Taylor, Demetria. Cushman's Sandwich Book. Lynn, MA: Cushman Bakery, undated.
    C. Y. Schelly & Bro. 52 Select Mme. Rambeau Recipes. Place of publication unknown: C. Y. Schelly & Bro., circa 1920s.
  - The D & C Company, Inc., 1928 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    D & C Co. Good Things to Eat. Brooklyn, NY: D & C Co., 1928.
  - D & L Slade Company, 1907-1920s (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
    D & L Slade Co. Slade's Guide to Good Cooking. Second Edition. Boston, MA: D. & L. Slade Co., 1907.
    D & L Slade Co. Patriotic Cook Book. Boston, MA: D. & L. Slade Co., circa 1918.
    D & L Slade Co. How to Make Salads and Sandwiches. Boston, MA: D & L Slade Co., undated.
    D & L Slade Co. Slade's Cooking School Recipes.Together with a Collection of 1912, Third edition. Boston, MA: D. & L. Slade Co. 1912.
    D & L Slade Co. Slade's Cooking School Recipes. Boston, MA: D. & L. Slade Co., 1916.
  - Dairy / Infants / Milk Research, 1887-1958 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Daniell, Olive C., 1885 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Davis Gelatine (Canada) Limited, 1932 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Davis' Baking Powder, 1904 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Davis' OK Cook Book
  - Delineator Home Institute, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - D. Everett Hale's Service Bureau, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - DeLand & Company--Cap Sheaf Soda, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    DeLand & Co. Cap Sheaf Brand Cook Book. Fairport, NY: DeLand & Co., undated. circa 1894.
  - Del Corte Coffee; Dixie Boy Brand, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Delmarva Poultry Industry, Inc., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Del Monte; California Fruit Canners Association; National Canners Association; California Packing Corporation, 1910-circa 1930 (Box 44, Folder 4, Box 11, Folder 2-3)
    California Fruit Canners Association. California Fruit and Vegetable Products with Recipes for their Use. San Francisco, CA: California Fruit Canners Association, 1915.
    Del Monte; California Packing Corporation. Conklin, Hester M., and Pauline D. Partridge. Del Monte Recipes of Flavor. Sixth edition. San Francisco, CA: California Packing Corporation, 1923.
    Del Monte; California Packing Corporation. Conklin, Hester M., and Pauline D. Partridge. Del Monte Recipes of Flavor. Publication No. 610. San Francisco, CA: California Packing Company, circa 1930.
    National Canners Association. Harland. The Story of Canning and Recipes. Place of publication unknown: National Canners Association, 1910.
    Del Monte; California Packing Corporation. The Del Monte Fruit Book: A Picked Collection of Recipes Covering the Best & Most Practical Service of Canned Fruits for Every Occasion. First Edition. San Francisco, CA: California Packing Corporation 1924.
    Del Monte; California Packing Corporation. The Del Monte Fruit Book Containing the Favorite Fruit Recipes of America's Best Known Cooking Authorities. Fourth edition. San Francisco, CA: California Packing Corporation, 1929.
    Del Monte, California Packing Corporation with Hester M. Conklin, Pauline D. Partridge. Del Monte Tomato Sauce Recipes: A Book of Over 100 Practical, Economical And Conveniently Made Dishes For All Occasions, Illustrating the Wide Usefullness And Almost Unlimited Possibilities of Del Monte Tomato Sauce in the Improvement of Every-Day Cooking. San Francisco, CA: California Packing Corporation, 1925.
  - Derby Foods, Inc.--Peter Pan Peanut Butter; Leony C. Derouet, 1919, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Derby Foods Inc. Peter Pan Peanut Butter in Your Daily Diet; A Book of Choice Recipes and Important Nutritional Information. Chicago, IL: Derby Foods Inc., undated.
    Derby. Peter Pan Peanut Butter Cook Book. Place of publication unknown: Derby Foods, Inc., 1963.
  - De Stewart, Dona Eloisa Delgado; Dewey & Almy Chemical Company, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Dewey & Almy Chemical Company. Thickit Stiff in a Minute. Cambridge, MA: Dewey & Almy Chemical Company, undated.
  - D. Ghirardelli Company with Anna Wells Morrison, circa 1900 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    D. Ghirardelli Co. "Try these Recipes with Ghirardelli's Ground Chocolate." Place of publication unknown: D. Ghirardelli Co., undated.
  - Diamond Walnut Growers, Inc., circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Diamond Walnut Growers, Inc. Diamond Walnut Recipe Gems. Stockton, CA: Diamond Walnut Growers, Inc., undated.
  - Dietrich Foods, Inc., circa 1980s-1990s (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Dietrich Foods, Inc. Barb Dietrich's "Make Every Day a Picnic". New York, NY: Dieterich Foods, Inc., undated.
  - The Dining Room Magazine, Vol II., No. 12, 1877 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dinsmore Manufacturing Company; Doliber-Goodale Company, 1883, 1887 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Dinsmore Manfg. Co. Price List and Cooking Receipts for the Florence Oil Cooking & Heating Stoves. Boston, MA: Dinsmore Manfg Co., 1883.
    Doliber-Goodale Co. Mellin's Food for Infants and Invalids. Boston, MA: Doliber-Goodale Co., undated.
  - Domestic Sewing Machine Company, 1882 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Domestic Sewing Co. Filomena Fairy. Portland, OR: Domestic Sewing Co., 1882.
  - Dormeyer Corporation, circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Dormeyer. Over 100 Delicious Recipes for Your Dormeyer Fri-Well Automatic Electric Cooker-Fryer. Chicago, IL: Dormeyer Corporation, undated.
  - Douglas-Pectin Corporation--Certo Corporation, 1923, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Certo. Recipes for Tempting Dishes Using Jams and Jellies. Rochester, NY: Certo Corporation, 1929.
    Douglas-Pectin Corporation. Bradley, Alice. Jams, Jellies and Marmalades made with Certo. Rochester, NY: Douglas-Pectin Corporation, 1923.
  - Dover Stamping Company; Drake, Samuel Adams, 1886 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Dover Stamping Company. The Dover Cook Book. Boston, MA: Dover Stamping Company, undated.
  - Dr. Bennett's Magnetic Quick Cure, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Dr. D. Jayne & Son, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Dr. D. Jayne and Son, comp. A Handbook How to Do Pickling. Philadelphia, PA: Dr. D. Jayne and Son, 1917.
  - Dr. Earl S. Sloan, 1901 (Box 11, Folder 17, Box 44, Folder 16)
    Sloan. Sloan's Y Hints and Up-to-date Cookbook. Boston, MA: Dr. Earl S. Sloan, 1901.
  - Dr. Herrick & Company, 1869 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Dr. J. C. Ayer & Company, 1892 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Ayer & Co. Ayer's Preserve Book. Lowell, MA: Dr. J. C. Ayer & Co., undated.
    Ayer & Co. Ayer's Book of Pies and Puddings. Lowell, MA: Dr. J. C. Ayers, 1892.
  - Dr. Miles Medical Company, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Miles Medical Company. Home Economy. Elkhardt, IN: Miles Medical Co., circa 1918.
    Miles Medical Company. Dr. Miles' Cook Book. Elkhart, IN: Dr. Miles Medical Company, undated.
  - Dr. Miles Medical Company, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Dr. Miles' Cook Book
  - Dr. M. M. Fenner Company, 1903, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    M. M. Fenner. Dr. Fenner's Peoples Remedies for the Family. Fredonia, NY: M. M. Fenner, 1903.
    M. M. Fenner Co. Dr. Fenner's Cook Book. Fredonia, NY: M. M. Fenner Co., undated.
  - Dr. Mosses Dame, circa 1900 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    Dr. Dame. Nature's Gifts Cookbook. New York, NY: Dr. Mosses Dame, undated.
  - Dr. Oetker's Einsiede Hilfe, circa 1920-1950s (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - D. Ransom & Company, 1869-1873 (Box 12, Folder 1, Box 11, Folder 24)
    Ransom. D. Ransom & Co.'s Family Receipt Book. Buffalo: D. Ransom & Co., 1868.
    Ransom. D. Ransom & Co.'s Family Receipt Book. Buffalo: D. Ransom & Co., 1869.
    Ransom. D. Ransom & Co.'s Family Receipt Book. Buffalo: D. Ransom & Co., 1870.
    Ransom. D. Ransom & Co.'s Family Receipt Book. Buffalo: D. Ransom & Co., 1871.
    Ransom. D. Ransom & Co.'s Family Almanac and Receipt Book. Buffalo: D. Ransom & Co., 1871.
    Ransom. D. Ransom & Co.'s Family Almanac and Receipt Book. Buffalo: D. Ransom & Co., 1872.
    Ransom. D. Ransom, Son & Co's Family Almanac and Receipt Book 1873. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1873.
  - D. Ransom Son & Company, 1874-1925, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2-12, Box 13, Folder 1)
    Ransom. Family Receipt Book 1874. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1874.
    Ransom. Family Receipt Book 1875. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1875.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1876. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1876.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1877. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1877.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1878. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1878.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1879. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1879.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1880. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1880.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1881. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1881.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1882. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1882.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1883. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1883.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1884. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1884.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1885. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1885.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1886. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1886.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1887. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1887.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1888. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1888.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1889. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1889.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1890. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1890.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1891. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1891.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1892. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1892.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1893. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1893.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1894. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1894.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1895. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1895.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1896. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1896.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1897. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1897.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1898. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1898.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1899. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1899.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1900. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1900.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1901. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1901.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1902. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1902.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1903. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1903.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1904. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1904.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1905. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1905.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1906. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1906.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1907. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1907.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1908. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1908.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1909. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1909.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1910. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1910.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1911. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1911.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1912. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1912.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1913. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1913.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1914. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1914.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1915. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1915.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1916. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1916.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1917. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1917.
    D. Ransom Son & Co. Ransom's Illustrated Encyclopedia Facts. Buffalo, NY: D. Ransom, Son & Co., circa 1880.
    Ransom. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1920-21. Buffalo: D. Ransom, Son & Co., 1920-21.
    D. Ransom Son & Co. Ransom's Family Receipt Book 1924. Buffalo: Baker, Jones Hausauer, Printers and Binders, Inc., 1924-1925.
  - Dr. R. V. Pierce--World's Dispensary Medical Association, 1898, 1900, 1909 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    World's Dispensary Medical Association. Pierce's Memorandum and Account Book Designed for Farmers, Mechanics and All People. Buffalo, NY: World's Dispensary Medical Association, 1898.
    World's Dispensary Medical Association. Pierce's Memorandum and Account Book Designed for Farmers, Mechanics and All People. Buffalo, NY: World's Dispensary Medical Association, 1909.
  - D. Shumway, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    D. Shumway. Shumway's Universal Recipe Book. Cuyahoga Falls, OH: D. Shumway, 1879.
  - The D. S. McDonald Company; Dulane, Inc., circa 1900, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Dulane Inc. Over 100 Recipes for Taste-Tempting Deep Fried Foods; Made Right with Fryryte Original Automatic Electric Deep Fryer. River Grove, IL: Dulane Inc., 1950.
    McDonald Co. The Story of a Silver Kettle. Boston, MA: D. S. McDonald Co., undated.
  - Dunbar & Company--Popcorn; Dunbar-Dukate Company--G.W. Dunbar's Sons, 1915-1927 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Dunbar & Co. Established 1900. "Steam Operated Popcorn Wagons & Poppers and Peanut Roasters 1927 Catalog." Chicago, IL: Dunbar & Co, 1927. Reprint, New York: The Vestal Press, undated.
    Dunbar-Dukate Co. Original Dunbar Shrimp. New Orleans, LA; Biloxi, MS: G. W. Dunbar's Sons, after 1915.
  - Dunham Manufacturing Company--Cocoanut, circa 1882 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Dunham Manufacturing Co. Dunham's Patent Concentrated Cocoanut. St. Louis, MO: Dunham Manufacturing Co., circa 1882.
    Durham's Original Shred Cocoanut. Rorer, Sarah Tyson, and Alice Cary Waterman. Delicious Desserts. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - D.W. Hull, 1869 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Dwinnel-Wright Company; Dynamics Corporation of America--Waring Products, 1916, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Dynamics Corporation of America. Waring Cook Book for the 8 Push Blender. New Hartford, CT: Waring Products, Dynamics Corporation of America, 1968.
    Dynamics Corporation of America. Your Waring Cookbook; The Pleasure of Blending. New Hartford, CT: Waring Products, Dynamics Corporation of America, 1969.